(Raj:)I'm a walking, brown yelp.com.
(Sheldon:)Structure, constant structure.
One atom.
(Howard:)Boy, he's really gone, isn't he?
(Leonard:)Yeah. This morning he used
a stick of butter as deodorant.
(Howard:)I thought I smelled popcorn.
(Sheldon:)The same as fermions.
Travels on a pathway.
Hexagonal. Always hexagonal.
(Leonard:)I haven't seen him this stuck since he
tried to figure out the third Matrix movie.
[SHELDON GASPS]
(Raj(as Sheldon reaches out and grabs from his plate):)Hey. Those are my lima beans.
(Sheldon:)Not lima beans. Carbon atoms.
(Raj:)But if I don't eat my lima beans,
I can't have my cookie.
(Leonard:)Here. You want my peas?
Peas. Perfect. They can be electrons.
You want my corn?
(Sheldon:)Don't be ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)What would I do with corn?
(Howard:)Roller skating.
Shall we grab a bite to eat first?
(Howard:)Good. P.F. Chang's?
My mom has coupons.